Lady Toki, I received news
of Lord Odin's demise.
They say he died a heroic death.
Toki, I see the end coming.
If I fail to defeat Kaido,
It will be a long time before a
challenger as strong as I appears.
And if hope does arrive, it
will come in twenty years.
I believe a massive war will erupt,
frightful enough to split the seas.
In the midst of that conflict,
powerful figures will fight
their way into the new world,
riding the waves of freedom.
They will be the ones to defeat Kaido.
A long winter is coming
to the land of Wano.
Toki, if I am to die in this struggle,
I want you to use your power.
Take these home.
Enma and Amenohavakiri.
I want our children to inherit them.
The children are a bit young, not to
mention small, to be swinging a sword.
I was sentenced to death, you know.
Why so nonchalant?
You won't die.
Not my husband.
That's my wife.
I'd be a laughingstock, if
anyone saw me crying now.
I'm a Kozuki as well.
That will not be your weakness.
Let us look to the future together.
20 years from now, we'll win.
If I have a dream, I
won't be able to do it.
I'll be laughing at the
birthday of the night.
Shut it up!
I don't want to break my heart.
I don't want to do it.
3DL.
I can't believe that I can't believe it.
It's worth it.
Dreaming on.
Up you go!
That's way too high!
Odin, stop! Please!
This is how wide the world
is, even from high in the sky.
You cannot see it all.
Quite the miracle, is it not?
Take a good look at all the things
you cannot find in the land of Wano.
It's so shiny, like treasure
sparkling in the sea!
Treasure, you say?
Seems you and I think alike.
You take after your father already?
I shall teach you all I know, Momonosuke.
You must broaden your knowledge.
Broaden your horizons!
So tell me, my boy, what
kind of women do you like?
He's too young!
When you cut a man down,
think of him as a fish cake!
Understand?
He's way too young!
Ah, that's beautiful, Hiyori.
You've gotten so good at playing. Really?
The song's called Moon Princess.
I'm going to try to get even better.
Good.
Keep it up.
You can play it at my funeral someday.
Hey, Momo, stop making your sister cry.
You're the one who made her cry. Me?
The funeral thing?
I'm sorry, it was only a joke.
Promise?
Like I die and leave you.
Well, my lord, how was the outside world?
Its splendors are difficult
to express with words.
But every day was a grand adventure!
Did you Karoo happen to see Zo?
Yes!
Wouldn't dare miss it! After all,
the people of Zo and the Kozuki Clan have
held a strong bond for many, many years.
I was impressed by the strength and
loyalty of the minks that I met there.
If you're in a pinch,
Zo is the place to go!
I'm sure you can count on
them to lend a helping paw!
What do you mean, in a pinch?
A pinch is a pinch. You'll know.
I'm sure I can count on you
two to save the day as well.
Now I'm starting to blush.
Better make sure we don't disappoint.
Right, Cat?
I've come to help.
Be at ease, friends.
I've collected your weapons for you.
We are saved.
You all must survive.
This country's future depends on you.
Well, we shall certainly try.
You have my thanks.
But of course, this is nothing.
Odin Castle, that's our goal!
Jakuri!
Yeah!
Serf King, one wreath question.
Could I be one of the Kozuki
clan's retainers as well?
We all forced ourselves into
the position, quite honestly.
So the choice is up to you, right?
Look here, they are the samurai.
We're not done!
What?!
Why don't Yugara want
me to fight the enemy?
Perhaps Yugara are a spy!
Kaido said he might have one!
Nonsense!
You, Karoo, taunted Kaido
and brought this upon us!
Lord Odin might still be
alive if not for your errands!
That's a damn lie!
We're going to so with or without you!
They'll die before they get there.
After you gotta stab them in the back.
Stop that at once.
Both of you.
Now is not the time.
Dogstorm, Cat Viper.
Damn it, what now?
What is that thing?
I fear we cannot aid them.
We must escape.
There are too many of them.
Let's thin them out. You ready? Of course.
Digital!
Ashura!
I'll go and back them up.
Run away!
To Olin' Castle!
Fire the arrows.
Mother, I'm scared.
Don't worry.
I'll make certain both of you escape.
Just hold on.
I know what to do.
Mother, no!
Mother, wake up!
Please, wake up!
What's your name?
It's too late!
I'm scared!
Someone help me!
I don't want to die!
Your father was a fool of a lord.
Your death will mark the
end of the Kozuki clan.
You're wrong!
Your father's a great man, Momonosuke.
And one day, my father was,
he was a great samurai, and one day,
the Kozuki clan shall rule
this country once more,
and I will be the Shogun.
Shallow words and likely not your own.
A dream stuffed in your head.
I didn't know that you were so young.
Father, somebody help!
I've lost interest.
To think that's Odin's son.
Let him burn to ash,
along with the castle.
It is with heavy heart
I must relay this news.
Despite our greatest
efforts, Lord Odin was slain.
Lift your heads. Let's leave.
It's dangerous here.
There's no time.
No, I shall remain behind.
Reconsider!
Please, it's not too
late to flee, Lady Toki.
Lady Toki, it is our honor to protect
you as long as we draw a breath.
I beg you!
Leave to the future.
Live on.
The what?
Who was that?
Shoot him down!
Toki, I know why you came
here from 800 years ago.
You wanted to witness it for yourself.
The whole world turning upside down.
And you should jump 20
years into the future.
The day you see...
No dinner for you today.
What a pity.
Oh, well, that's only fair
since I'm not making any money.
That's not why.
Then what?
Just tell me.
Because you said something awful.
It's scary, like something's wrong.
What's this bad feeling, Grandma?
This is the end.
We turned our back on Lord Odin.
and now the gods have
turned their backs on us.
It's just the beginning of an endless
night for all of Wano and its people.
Odin, I came here because I
was running from the past.
I always believed if I came to the future,
there would be someone waiting.
someone who could make a difference.
It's Lady Toki.
You are the moon, yet unaware
of the dawn.
May your purpose be fulfilled.
and cast nine shadows on
the night woven of 20 years,
and you shall know the
brilliance of the dawn.
Remember this, please.
Odin.
I wanted this water boiling hot.
It's as hot as it gets, I can assure you.
Don't you lie to me.
It's freezing! Freezing!
Freezing!
Oh, hot!
Look at my hand!
The water is scalding!
You're going to cook yourself!
I'm shivering cold!
I can't stop shaking!
I want the hands of those samurai!
I want their bones!
What's taking so long?!
I can't rest till I know they're dead!
All 20 years, Lady Toki, I
don't know who's alive or dead.
Princess, behold, the Cape dance.
No!
Hold it, pal.
What's with those clothes?
A bunch of filthy rags. I wonder.
Do you really live here in the capital?
Excuse me. We're sorry!
You're strong as hell!
Where did you come from?
Let us work underneath you!
What's your name, man?
My name...
Well, let's see.
Kyoshiro will do.
You're the Kyoshiro family?
Yes, sir.
You may lift your head now.
Your reputation is impeccable.
What do you say?
Want to serve as my guard?
Why, that would be an honor.
My lord.
Very good.
All is yours. Gold. Women.
Gods.
I so gladly provide everything
that you may desire.
Did you hear that?
I love this guy.
Where'd he come from?
Seems too good to be true.
He's a wealthy businessman,
and he's strong.
He's a yakuza.
He's taking boss Yoguro's place.
The Kyoshiro family
rules the flower capital.
He has a weakness, though.
Because he always looks tired, right?
That's why people call
him Napping Kyoshiro.
Too much nightlife is my bet.
Mitsushimin Shukazo!
He stole money from the storehouse again!
Princess!
Lady Hiyori!
Where did you go?
Please don't leave me!
Excuse me, boss.
We found this cute little
girl on the street.
She acted like she was lost.
Must be an orphan.
She's practically starving to death.
This may be hard to understand.
What? Denchiro? Really?
None other.
What a relief.
Denchiro.
Gaze upon my face.
Haunted by the Ghost of Wrath,
it's twisted into this shape.
Even Kin'emon and the others
would not recognize me.
And that is our strength.
This shall be our secret, held
till the day of the final battle.
Do not tell anyone about
me, even our allies.
I shall protect you in Kawamatsu's stead.
And you shall bear the name Komurasaki.
This is for you, Ushimitsu.
They just can't stop giving me money.
Don't be so reckless!
But thank you!
I shall distribute it in Ebisu Town.
By the way.
As I have told you many times.
You must always carry fake
blood under your kimono.
Orochi is fixated on you.
But he has no idea that
you're Lord Odin's daughter.
I know it's difficult.
But if something goes wrong?
I will tear Orochi away from
Komurasaki with your death.
It must be convincing enough that
the entire capital believes it.
I've survived for this long, haven't I?
It's been nearly 20 years.
The end is in sight.
Now, with the tale of Kozuki Oden at its
end, we arrive nearly at the present.
A few months before
Luffy and Oden's allies
come together for their
raid on Onigashima,
Orochi receives a note I know they were
real they're coming for me so talking
really could send people through time
so
those
people
went missing because
they shot forward through time not because
they burn with the castle someone's
trying to get out of your skin don't
let them read it this isn't a joke
keep a close eye on the coast
someone will try to leave
the country yes sir If what
you're saying turns out true,
then I don't want you to kill them.
After 20 years, there's something I want
to ask the remnants of the Kozuki clan.
So this report is the work
of your spy, I take it?
Is he reliable?
He is. Absolutely.
To a frightful degree, you might say.
He was born into a theater troupe.
and raised upon the stage
but one day thanks to the
same persecution that i
suffered parents were killed in
the middle of a performance
they said they're from the
same clan as the daimyo killer
served his life yeah yeah
the only way he survived was
by assuming different roles
that's right it's a pity your parents had
to die but i took revenge on their killers
and do we have so much
suffering yet to inflict
your new purpose is to
live your life among the
kozuki in the end you
will die as a member of
the kozuki clan without
anyone knowing the truth
I'm offering you a starring role Here on
the stage of history You're up for the job,
aren't you?
A miserable creature whose
only pleasure in life.
Is to become someone else.
Oh, and his skills served me well!
Whenever I borrowed money from Odin, he
always made sure I got twice as much.
If it wasn't for that money, I
couldn't have allied with you.
And the information he provided about
Odin's raid was quite helpful as well.
The man truly is insane.
He was there at Odin's execution,
ready to die with his enemies.
He has no will of his own.
So long as I tell him we'll play
the part of a loyal Kozuki Retainer,
mindlessly sending me
information all the while.
What a frightfully loyal servant he is.
The exploits of Kozuki
Oden have become legend.
Twenty years have passed
since his tragic demise.
The remaining members of the Kozuki Clan,
the Kurozumi, and Kaido continue
their struggle in the present day.
Odin's dream of opening the borders
lives on thanks to Toki's final act.
His retainers now take up
their swords in a new era.
For months, they risk their lives to recruit
allies who would join their struggle.
But their persistence pays off,
and 4,200 people stand at their side,
determined to liberate their country.
The weapons and ships are ready.
The troops are gathered.
At twilight, on the day
of the Fire Festival,
they prepare to depart from Tokage Port.
Their destination?
Onigashima!
We'll kick your ass!
But something has gone wrong.
Stop this madness!
You can't take that boat!
All of you will die and save!
We cannot throw away this opportunity.
The chance you speak of will
not occur for another year.
Kaido will use the full
strength of his army
to hunt down every last
rebel in the country.
No, wait! Stop! No!
Do not defy me!
Please, Kiriman! Ashura!
Kachuro! Raizo! Kong!
Of the 4,200 troops expected to
arrive, not even one is present.
There are signs of destruction
at the fort as well.
The storm is raging, but
the samurai push off.
Get back!
If you leave, you'll be
marching to your death!
Be careful!
Heed me, Lord Momonosuke!
We cannot alter here!
Though we may be few in number,
this will allow us to sneak
into their midst undetected.
Then I shall plunge my
sword into Kaido's neck.
As long as we live, we shall never relent.
How could it have come to this?
Does this not mean our
plan was leaked yet again?
I consider that.
In fact, I suspect that thought
has crossed all of our minds.
It pains me to even suggest this, but...
There may be an enemy among us, even now.
It is a truth.
I don't even want to battle.
Master Keen!
Where is the brave warrior I know?
You have one duty now.
Find the traitor!
Cut them off and let them go!
Otherwise, how can we proceed, but how can
we find them when they will not confess?
I agree with Kiku fully.
Let's put this to rest now.
For I was always the
traitor—what did you just say?
say
You were in that pot.
You nearly boiled to
death with the rest of us.
Indeed.
That would have been a wonderful
finale for a wonderful performance.
I played one of the Akazaya Nine, the evening
shower Kanjuro, Odin's loyal retainer.
But he was but a character upon a stage.
we shared our most
intimate joys and sorrows
i earned your trust my
intent was not to cause
you harm nor did i
resent you i only use to
feed information to lord
orochi again and again
how could that be you lied
to us since the day we
met how could you do this
you never knew my real
name.
Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Need I say more?
Remember when the first plan
was leaked? When you were
all so sure that laws subordinates talked?
Though I must credit Yasui for
his quick thinking, even if
it cost him his life, changing the
meeting spot was a brilliant strategy.
But as soon as that
Information made its way to me,
his sacrifice became meaningless.
Then there was.
Zoe, an island that one cannot
locate without a Vivre card.
And yet Jack happened upon it so
easily.
Didn't that strike you as odd?
Why didn't you suspect it was one of us?
You searched everywhere for answers,
but you never looked over your shoulder.
You knew something was amiss, but
you just couldn't connect the dots.
Look, it's just like Lord Orochi
said, a tiny bone and it's Onigashima.
What a bunch of idiots!
Whatever will they do?
I thought it was a joke, but they
really are the old Akasaya samurai.
But one of them's a spy
working for the Shogun, huh?
The one with the big grin, I'd guess.
None other.
Touch him out!
Imagine if we died sooner, my secret would
have sunk to the bottom of the ocean.
It would have been an honor
to play my role until the end;
however, Lord Orochi stopped me.
He said, "Well done—the
final act is finished.
I'm to seize the Momonosuke and
take him to Onigashima!" onigashima
Get him on! Help me!
Unhand him now!
How did Kanjido get to the port?
Wait! No!
If he's on the shore, then this
Kanjido must be... ancient!
But the Kanjuro we know has
never entered in such detail!
Seriously, you two?
How are you dozing off at
a time like this? Get up!
Huh?
Are the repairs wrapped up yet?
Now that I had a nap, I just need
dinner so I can kick them off!
What's going on? Let her rip!
Sir Luffy? Hey guys!
Sorry we're a little late!
Who are they?
I thought that we sank
all the enemy ships.
What happened?
There's something underneath the boat!
Who the hell takes a crappy little
rowboat out in this kind of weather?
It's you!
Don't take the sea lightly, dumbasses!
They're attacking from the other side now.
Why did I see all those ships and samurai?
Hanging out at the port
like a bunch of idiots!
What are they doing? What?
Another ship?
I almost sank them.
Because they were in my friggin' way.
You're still alive.
And all your crewmates as well.
I didn't think you'd
bother to show, Jaggy.
Go to hell!
I am only here to take Kaido's head!
What's happening?
How are they here?
How was I left unaware of this plan?
Luffy!
We weren't expecting this!
They made it sound like we were only
dealing with a couple of samurai and a robo!
I wasn't ready to fight pirates!
It's the worst generation!
I thought they were locked up!
Listen up, jerks!
Stop messing with the samurai's boat!
The sea was made for pirates like us!
Thank you.